Welcome back. Now after our hard work, our climbing system is finally coming together.
欢迎回来。现在，经过我们的努力，我们的攀登系统终于组装在一起了。
And now we have working locomotion for climbing. We can hop up, we can hop down,
现在我们有了可以工作的攀岩运动。我们可以跳起来，我们可以跳下来，
we can enter and exit the climb state, and we can also climb up and climb down the ledge.
我们可以进入和退出攀爬状态，也可以爬上爬下悬崖。
And if we want, when our character is near a vaultable surface, we can start vaulting.
如果我们愿意，当我们的角色接近可跳跃的表面时，我们可以开始跳跃。
And that's a really cool feature. And the last thing that I want to do,
这真的是一个很酷的功能。我最不想做的事就是
so I'm going to disable the capsule shape. I don't need to see it anymore.
所以我要禁用胶囊形状。我不需要再看到它了。
So go back to my character blueprint. Inside of this capsule component,
所以回到我的角色蓝图吧。在该胶囊组件的内部，
I'm going to take this hidden in game, click compile, and click play.
我将把这个隐藏在游戏中，点击编译，然后点击播放。
And now we can really have fun with our climbing system.
现在我们可以真正享受我们的攀岩系统带来的乐趣了。
Congratulations on getting this far, and I'd like you to pat yourself on the back.
祝贺你走到这一步，我希望你能拍拍自己的后背。
These are not some easy features to create. And with the tools and knowledge you have now,
创建这些功能并非易事。有了你现在所拥有的工具和知识，
you can pretty much add in any other features that you see fit in here.
你几乎可以在这里添加你认为合适的任何其他功能。
And I really can't wait to see what you come up with next.
我真的迫不及待想知道你下一步会做什么。
So go try out your own ideas, and most importantly, have fun with our climbing system.
所以去尝试你自己的想法，最重要的是，享受我们的攀岩系统。